https://bruinsmontessori.com/privacy-notice/

Account
Bruins Montessori International USA Inc.
Search:
Search
Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Account
Wishlist
Log In
Menu
About UsProducts Practical LifeSensorialMathematicsBotanyLanguageGeographyFurnitureMiscellaneousPAMS ItemsSparesClassroom PackagesAgentsConferencesContact Us
Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for Bruinsmontessori only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Collection of Information We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors.
Cookie/Tracking Technology The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.
Distribution of Information We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact Information If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By e-mail: info@bruinsmontessori.com By Phone:1-800-990-9012
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
Main Categories
About UsProductsPractical LifeSensorialMathematicsBotanyLanguageGeographyFurnitureMiscellaneousPAMS ItemsSparesClassroom PackagesAgentsConferencesContact Us
Bruins Montessori
Bruins Montessori USA provides a wide range of Montessori products at our distribution center in Dallas, Texas. Our friendly staff and well equipped store provides easy and convenient access for our customers.
Business hours are Monday-Friday 8:30am to 5:00pm CST
We ship through UPS
Call us now: 214 337 2622
Furniture may incur additional shipping charges.
All Metal Fractions are Laser Cut.
Bruins Montessori International USA Inc, 4651 S. Westmoreland Rd, Dallas TX 75237
CALL : 1-800-990-9012 PHONE : 214-337-2622 FAX : 214-337-6226 E-MAIL :bruins@bruinsmontessori.com
March 22 – 25,
Sheraton Denver Downtown,
Denver, CO
Subscribe to our mailing list to get updates to your email inbox
Subscribe
Copyright © 2017 Bruins. All Rights Reserved.
